[music]
H hello everyone.
Hello. Hello.
Mate,
[laughter]
mate. Um, another another day, another
series of issues when booting up a
stream. Wow.
[laughter and gasps]
Wow.
Hello.
How's everyone doing? Okay, it's
connected. Okay.
72.
Not there. How's everyone doing? So, uh
I know it's a bit late.
Um Bes Hello.
Hello.
Um
there's
the way. What was the issue again? What
the
Hello, Franco. Welcome to the stream.
Hello. Hello.
Hello.
Q.
I need to fix that. I need to fix that.
Hello, Rango. Uh, one second. Give me a
minute.
78. What is 78?
Oh my god.
Wait. Oh. Oh. Oh. I'm so dumb. Oh.
Oh.
Oh. This is wrong. Okay. Okay. Okay. I
fixed I fixed it. I fixed it. Okay. Save
it.
I know for Discord people, uh, you
haven't got an announcement. I'm working
on it. Uh, this this automation thing is
supposed to work. Ah, so many issues.
All right. Twitch. How's Twitch doing?
Twitch is live. Right. Okay.
What? Let me check. Uh chat.
Uh
hello Franco. How you doing? Welcome.
Welcome.
Okay. Kick. How's Kick doing? Kick is
also doing well. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Uh, I can peacefully
close all of these stuff and like focus
on stream finally.
Yay.
[snorts]
Oh boy. So much things.
Yesterday
uh yeah yesterday we I faced a lot of
issues. No. So, I spend like a bit uh
working on fixing all the bugs and then
I went to sleep really late by the way.
So, that's why today uh instead of doing
a morning stream like around this time
I'm supposed to be like doing my
revision thing for my exams, Japanese
exam. I kind of did it in the morning a
little bit and
yeah. Hi. Anyway, let me switch to the
game. Oh, a scenery [music] changed
happened. Okay.
Hi. A new update of our creators is
here.
And uh you do not see the game.
Uh
there you go.
Is it audible? Okay, now it's working.
Hi. New update. A new update. I I just
finished updating the game.
I finished updating the game and it's
here. Yay.
Uh,
close that.
Give me a minute.
Need to double check something.
Yeah, it's running. Hi. Uh, okay. What's
What's this? I have a meal. 10 million
raiders. It's been a hell of a ride so
far. We're celebrating it. A huge
milestone. 10 million raiders in a rust
belt. Oh, it's a golden pickaxe.
Right. Humble by your love traders. Uh
there's so much more exciting content to
come. Um so you so we hope you stay for
journey for the first 10 million. So
here's something short for it. Yes.
Thank you.
Yeah, new new n new new raider tool.
Let's go.
The golden one.
Look guy.
Nice. I I like the hockey uh the goalie
decks. This is nice. It's kind of bit
longer and nice. Yeah, this is the paid
one.
Not bad.
Ritual stuff. Yeah, this is also I I
like the hokey one. So, I feel like this
is the basic raider tool,
but golden edition.
[laughter]
Nice.
Yeah, Scrappy has different kinds, you
know. So, white, black, um, yellow,
orange, brown. I have this one,
you know. Nice.
Nice.
Hi. We're almost a million. Uh,
if I'm correct,
there is no even left. Trials is there.
I'm still behind on trials. I have to
get my stuff back up, finish stuff, and
everything.
Um,
hidden bunger.
Oh, hidden bunger. Wait, wait, wait. We
need this. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh. Hidden bunger. Okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay. Oh, let's go to hidden
bunger. Uh, what do we have? Okay, I
have basic stuff. Um, you know what? I'm
going to go free load out.
I'm going to go preload out.
Yeah.
One second.
Give me a minute.
>> Okay. Save this.
My chat. You have to be there.
Okay.
All right. Did the announcement ever get
sent? No, it didn't. Right. Ah, it did
not.
It's going to send 15 minutes. Yeah. All
right. We're still queuing.
Wow.
Perfect.
Okay, we got a match.
>> Okay, let's go.
Hey, good job.
Okay, I also did the Instagram thingy
[sighs]
and got it overloaded. My fishy.
Okay, let me close the brow first.
Hey,
question. Where is the hidden bunker
event again?
Antenna.
>> Anyone near the spaceport? Someone just
managed to override bunker security
system and every
go to waste.
>> Okay.
Uh
outskirts, right? Outskirts. Okay.
Outskirts.
We are going in.
My FPS is dropping like crazy, man.
So,
I believe this antenna is the thing I
have to go right.
Uh in wait which is the bunker? Who is
the bunker?
How bastion is there?
For now, I would just go towards the um
departure building and get on top of the
antenna and see what's up.
Is that a spotter or a snitch?
>> Snitch.
Oh, my buttons are in Valerant.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
>> Don't shoot.
Attention
raiders. The south antenna has just been
activated.
ATTENTION
RAIDERS, the east ANTENNA HAS BEEN
SUCCESSFULLY ACTIVATED.
WAIT, WAS I MUTED this whole time?
Wait, was I muted this whole time? What
the heck?
I am dead. I am dead. I'm dead. I am
dead.
>> I am dead.
I can't deal with this. No, I I
help.
HEY,
>> don't kill him in a half.
>> Please help.
Okay,
thank you.
>> Oh my god, these guys are friendly.
These guys are actual friendlies.
Where is the bunger?
Uh, wait. The antennas.
Wait, the antennas are
Oh my god.
Wait, did someone actually kill the
bastion?
I'll get on too.
>> Oh, actually someone killed it.
>> Attention all raiders. The west antenna
has been successfully activated.
>> What I could do now is to
Hey.
>> HELLO, RAIDER.
HEY, DON'T SHOOT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
Get some good stuff from here. Thank you
very much.
>> Goop goop.
I take them all.
Let them have the rest. I don't want it.
>> Why are you leaving without doing the
bunker stuff?
>> Let's go to that antenna.
>> I do not have any heals, don't I?
And that is a bit bad.
So, one would ask
Doc next, what's the game plan here? So,
my plan is to get the antenna here
and see how that goes.
Apparently, you have to
get uh Oh my lord. Rocketeer.
Apparently, you have to unlock.
>> Attention raiders. The north antenna has
been activated.
>> Uh yeah, the antenna.
>> Don't shoot.
>> What? Why did he shoot at me?
The heck.
Also, did the announcement ever get
made? Oh my god, it's taking so much
time.
>> Don't shoot.
Oh, there are people trying to do the
hidden bunker.
>> DON'T SHOOT.
ALL RIGHT.
Please don't kill me.
>> Just a passing stranger.
Wait, how are you supposed to get
through the antenna up here?
Uh,
wait. How does one get up there? I do
not have the snap rope, though.
Wait,
wait. How are you supposed to get up
there?
What?
Since I'm here, I want to check on
something.
What happened to my Discord
announcement?
Why is it skipping? Hey
H.
Okay.
Not this.
But how to get on top though?
Wait, it's open.
M the antenna is gone.
Wait. Do you mean to say it's open?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
>> Let's go to that location. Oh,
>> it's open.
I know my game is lagging.
Easy is stuffed.
Oh [\h__\h]
Ah, both of them are there. Ah.
Run for your life. Run for your life.
Run for your life.
How do I get inside the bunker?
Oh my god. Sammy, get out of here.
So, is this the bunker? Question mark.
Uh,
I hear pe people.
Hey, don't shoot.
There are some people here,
it seems.
So, where is the bunker?
This feels like a bunker.
Hidden bunker. Where?
Uh
Hey, don't shoot.
>> All right.
>> Hey there.
>> Oh, this guy was doing the
the B thing.
But where is the bunker?
I think I should Google this.
M
our creators
hidden bunker location.
Oh.
Oh, I'm in the wrong location. Stupid.
It's here.
>> Let's go to that location.
Oh,
never mind. I didn't know.
your lines. Uh
oh, here to
I just want to survive, man. Somehow,
honestly, speaking.
It's my first time doing this event.
Oh, I hear it.
I hear that.
Where is it?
Hey, don't shoot.
Oh, I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I
see. I see. I see. I see. I see it. I
see it. I see it. I see it. I see it.
So this is the hidden bunker.
How to get out of here.
Don't shoot.
Let me live.
Question. Where is the thingy I have to
download from?
Okay,
I have to wait for this guy to finish
downloading or something.
Otherwise,
hello there.
Hello.
What do I do though? I I don't get it.
Is there any other
is that the only place?
Hello.
Oh, thank you.
So I did on.
There's an empty place over here.
>> OKAY.
So
download information from the bunker at
the
So I did that. Now what
So it has to be
uh yellow.
I'm so confused.
Oh my god. Oh.
Oh, here.
So, I did this. Now what? I just wait.
Wait, I have to Google this or
something.
Download information
from
inside
bunker.
Bunker arc
raiders.
Oh, there's eight of these. Oh,
now this is off.
Oh,
okay. I I got one. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. I understand. I understand
now.
Wait. Uh.
Okay. I understand now. So, I have to
wait.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Oh,
got it. That's how it is.
I just have to wait
and not run around.
Interesting.
It has a big weight times, doesn't it?
Oh, like this. Okay, one more and we go.
I can't take that. Oh,
I need one more.
Okay,
I just wait here.
>> An arc orbiter is on route. Safe window
is closing. 10 minutes to get out of
there. I
>> Where should I extract?
I have to go here, huh? Head home at the
east elevator.
Now that I know the location, I can
always come here.
Yeah.
Uh,
I think I would need one more.
I kind of am thinking that I would need
one more.
Yeah, I would need one more. Dang it.
Okay, this will be the last
we wait
and I do my best to extract and we are
Gucci.
No matter what happens, we have to
extract them.
Hey there.
Thank you.
Okay, let's leave.
How do I leave again?
This way.
Oh my lord. Please.
Oh [\h__\h]
Okay. Slowly, steadily, slow and steady
wins the race.
Hey, don't shoot.
>> All raiders, we have arc on screen. 5
minutes left. Go find a way home. I
repeat, 5 minutes.
>> Yes, I'm trying to find a way home.
>> Oh my god. No.
Oh my god,
the game crashed the [\h__\h] hell,
bro.
>> Don't shoot.
Oh my god, I cursed. I'm sorry. I'm so
stressed right now.
>> Don't shoot.
Oh my god.
Why is there a big wall of China over
here?
I just want to leave.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Why is that a big wall?
>> No.
Oh my god.
Thank you. Thank you. Someone
If he's going to kill it, I would love
to just get the
Oh my god, I just won the rocket there.
Oh no.
>> Last warning. 2 minutes left. Head back
immediately. The window is closing.
Security. I got your call. Stand by. I'm
sending the elevator.
I want to give this guy this.
Initiating.
>> Stand by.
>> Let's head home at the east.
>> Get in. Get in.
Okay, it's fine. It's fine. I'll take I
I couldn't drop him. I wanted to give
him He gave me an anvil, though. Oh,
but yeah, we finished the challenge.
By a close call. Oh boy.
He gave me a free anvil, bro. I'll take
it. I'll take it.
I'll take it.
Let's go.
No way. No way.
What,
bro?
No way. The best argu argument in the
game. I just got the blueprint from just
doing the trials. What?
What?
Oh my god. Nice. Hello, Solar.
Oh my god. We got the Aman,
bro.
Crazy.
We got the Aman.
How cool is that?
Okay, wait. Um, I have enough to
finish my explosive station,
>> but I can craft that light. Yeah,
let's go.
And uh,
three. Okay, refiner is left, right? And
bombeteer. I need the socket tree and
the morture.
So, we unlocked uh
Oh, wait, wait. I have to do it. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. We got the best argument in
the game, blueprint. So, learn and
consume.
Let's go. I can finally craft this. Yay.
So we need a lot of processor and
advanced electrical components. Yeah.
>> Oh god.
Okay. Um,
I think I could
bang event is still there.
We could uh try doing that again. Or
there's so many night rates, but we
can't play those
for some odd reason.
Um,
I feel like I could do it bunger again.
Not sure though.
We got this much done.
Hornets, pops, rocket,
carryables.
Um
the stuff
surveillance
control tower research administration.
Okay, I'm gonna lock in and we'll
try our best to
we'll try our best to like
um
I want to
electrical not
with electricals. Um,
let's trickles.
I do want to use a Valencia.
I want to use the blue uh blue or the
purple one though. I want to get as much
as stuff there.
I have to make sure I am safe safe and
do not die.
And the thing is I'm streaming right
now. I don't trust myself when I stream.
As in I've been the unluckiest of the
unluckiest.
Yeah.
Also, it never did the announcement,
right? Oh my god.
It never did the announcement.
Oh my
Lord,
there you go. Now I did the
announcement,
brother.
Okay, give me one second.
Okay.
Save this.
And uh
hello Aisen. Welcome,
welcome, welcome. Hello. Hello. How you
doing? I'm doing great. How are you?
Welcome.
How are you doing?
I don't want to use the big guns, but I
have to survive now.
So, what should I do?
Let's not start asking questions. Okay.
>> But I want to make money.
>> Why is your stream kind of chopped?
Wait, what do you mean stream kind of
chopped? Wait, what do you mean?
>> If you find any weapons just laying
around,
>> wait, chopped as in laggy. Quality low.
It's because my PC is dying.
Wait, is it chopped? What do you mean by
chop?
Uh, wait, wait, wait.
That's full. No, it's uh
elaborate.
Crop like I can only see middle part.
Oh, refresh your browser.
Refresh. Refresh.
O,
you're watching on YouTube shorts. Wait,
wait, wait. Click on my profile from
there.
And you go to the main horizontal
stream.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh you're watching the
You're watching from shorts.
You're watching from shots.
That's why you're watching from shots.
YouTube crops horizontal streams into
vertical uh short stream now. That's
why. Yeah.
So now you don't need to send a
different feed to
Oh,
but it'll be hard for people to
understand what's going on now.
I want to buy this, but I don't know.
I got to take this and I'll take No,
I'll take the federal.
Ah, I'll take this. Fine. And I'll
maybe take
uh
K. No, I don't have much kettals now.
I'll figure out.
So, medium and heavy ammo.
Heavy. One stack. Medium.
two stack. Maybe
I'll go like this. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And
we need uh shields.
>> Oh, don't lie. You just came here to see
little old me, didn't you?
>> Uh
I'll take five of them. Thank you very
much.
Try not to do that. this like this.
Okay. Cuz we are out of money. We need
to make money.
Uh
show you.
Oh, there's night raid happening here.
There's night raid.
What if I die? I don't want to die.
I want to do this.
My nitrate is also nice though.
Okay, if I'm going to boo, what's going
to happen? We we need to literally go to
village, scour through everything, exit
via the hatch key, right? We are going
for money making, right?
So Oh, if that's the case, let's not
take this. We'll take the hatch key.
Take one hatch key with us and
shield. Everything is good. AO. Okay.
So, I should be
technically good.
Yeah. Hi. Uh, let's do night ray then.
Let's hope and pray that we get spawned
somewhere safer.
And, um, just for safety, I'll take some
bandages.
Rest of it, I'll Yeah.
Let's go.
I have to use these. No, I'll do it
later.
So, we finished the hidden mang. Oh, I
thought
I
I'll eat some orange
while we're loading into the game
cuz I'm hungry though.
I did have my dinner,
but yeah, a little bit hungry.
>> Okay, we got spawned on about something.
>> Have your eyes adjusted to the dark yet,
Raider?
>> Loot is right for the picking while most
of Toledo is asleep. Let's go to the
suppliers that ark is twice as vigilant
after sunset.
>> We could go to Pilgrim's Peak.
>> Let's go to the Pilgrim's Peak
>> actually cuz it's closer.
I just need to make sure I don't get
spotted cuz these guys are there. The
Pilgrim's Peak.
Those
guys can be nasty.
And as I said, I do not want to die.
That does n.
Oh, wait. That should be stuff over
here.
I could kill it.
Okay.
Oh [\h__\h] that's two rocket. Oh my lord.
Ah,
Dang it.
I do not want to die
a bad death.
No game, stop crashing.
I'm on the verge of the get dying over
here.
Oh god, they're turning around.
Bro, this is so scary.
If I had nades, nah, I could have just
killed them both and just call it the
day and extract.
But well,
oh, wait.
there. You can't extract with hats,
bro. I forgot it's a night ray.
Is someone shooting?
Don't shoot.
>> I have this weird feeling that
I'm late.
to the party
and it's already looted.
Oh, wait. It's not looted. Oh.
Okay, this one went close.
Someone's breaking the
Don't shoot.
I'm sure
it please.
We need uh processors, All right.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
>> Wait, did someone die?
I mean, it is a bit scary to
Wait, did someone die? Die.
I heard a radar flare.
Why are these stuff not loaded?
Oh. Oh. Oh.
Yes.
Crazy luck.
Now we need to get more processors.
Hey, he died.
He didn't have anything.
Got him.
Why did he come here then?
Aquin fan is needed. I want this.
Okay, we got 58k.
>> Basically, we're running for
>> HOMEARE
I want to play it safe. Actually,
>> don't shoot.
>> That snitch might be my nightmare.
Hey, don't shoot.
>> Okay, breach this.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Oh, it called the f. It called its
friends.
It did call his friends. Oh no.
Was better I leave, right? I got a lot
of stuff.
Don't shoot.
>> Did someone actually literally literally
literally shoot me? Wait, wait, wait,
wait. Did actually someone literally
literally shoot me?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Rewind it back. Wait, wait, wait. Let me
watch my shrimp. Wait,
wait, wait, wait a minute.
I was there. Someone literally shot me.
That's not an arc. That's actual player.
Wait.
Yeah, there's a player.
What? A player shot me.
Everyone, who is this guy?
Why you beeping, bro?
I'm supposed to be in the com
BB lobby.
[laughter]
Thank god I Thank God, man.
Thank god I I was able to extract
easily.
That's scary.
Oh, we need this,
this, this.
Uh,
damn, I got Wolf bag.
Crazy.
Nice.
Imagine the amount of more uh arcs I can
beat up here.
Yeah, it's it's going to be insane.
I got two of the good grenades now.
>> Now I can take down any arc I want.
>> And that is good,
>> right? Do not take it to the shower.
>> Got Yeah, I got the wolf pack blueprint.
I literally just now got the a wolf pack
blueprint. Yeah,
[laughter]
lucky I enjoy I obtain a night raid
and I was able to get it. Yeah.
Also, did the announcement for stream
sent to Wise? What the heck?
Why? Why? Why? Why didn't it make it
twice? Wait, I want to check this.
Why? Why is it twice?
Bro, you're not supposed to make it
twice. It's already mapped.
Uh
892.
Can I see a gun? Yeah. Yeah. Gun
station. Uh
I don't know how much I
[laughter]
don't have much.
Uh oh. I got to think a blue frame. Some
random stranger helped me with that.
Wait, I can you I I have van. Wow.
Jupiter. there.
This is Alfon.
You know, I need to get the Jupiter to
do the energy clip thingy. You uh craft
energy clips and sell it. Sell it. Sell
it to make millions.
So where will world
and most of the guns except get
legendary guns. Wow,
nice.
Uh also also I got this Dio. I I
literally I did the I did the trials.
No, but we can I did the hidden bunger
event. I did the hidden bunker event.
All you have to do is um
All you have to do is uh load into a
spaceport hidden bunker and the bunker
is supposed to be here somewhere, right?
And you wait till uh wait till you get
the thingy, download the data, extract
the data, get do four of them and you
finish it. I got this thing.
I got
I got survivor blueprint,
bro. I got survivor blueprint.
Crazy.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh
870.
Okay. One second.
Uh,
one second there. Copy ID.
this thing.
Okay, this god patch. Uh, this should
work now.
Let me run it once and check
it works or not.
How you doing, Bacon?
Also, how much money do you have in your
account now?
I have to get
1 mil.
1 1 mil. 5 mil. No, 6 million in total.
I'm space coins.
Space coins.
Not bank account.
[laughter]
Oh my god.
Why would I ask you about your bank
account?
Oh my god.
Should I go again?
>> Wait, if I go nade, no active. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, we need
we need our this thing.
I had to go over there.
Yeah, but let's do this and go,
make money, and come back home.
But wait, isn't Stella better for making
money?
>> Ah, never mind.
I do that.
And you know what? I'll do something
instead of selling the
um that um
those um Oh, someone died.
Instead of selling the arguments, right,
I'll keep it in my
machine to know anything for sure.
>> I'll keep them in my stash and then I
forgot to take the key with me.
I Yeah, I'll keep them in my stash
and
then I will
>> Oh, it's a late raid.
Hey, don't shoot.
Someone on top. Oh god.
>> Don't shoot.
BROTHER IN CHRIST.
OH, no one came here. Okay, good. Loot,
loot, loot, loot.
No one car go
after bridge for processing processes.
Oh, fried motherwoods also 4K. I will
take that.
Yeah, go go go.
I need the money.
Feels like someone's nearby.
We need the battery now.
You never know.
We're at the end.
Oh god, that's a thing.
Yeah, processors.
Ah, the game crashed or lagged again.
Okay, back. It's back.
Grenade pouch.
I need this. Uh,
how about this?
Take that as well.
I think someone's home.
I have a feeling someone is here.
Oh my lord. Yes.
I'll drop this.
Oh yes.
Oh my god. Okay. Uh
Don't shoot.
I felt like saying that cuz I felt like
someone is close.
And then we take this.
It's fully unloaded.
Oh, okay.
Ah, I'm so full.
I am so gooped up. [laughter]
[gasps]
Oh, what the heck?
I am so gooped up.
Uh,
I am so gooped up,
bro. I am so gooped up.
I am so gooped up
there.
Okay. How where do I go for extract?
Okay.
>> Head home at the water treatment
elevator.
>> I am so cooped up.
>> An Arc orbiter is on route. The safe
window is closing. You have 10 minutes
to return to Spiran. I repeat, 10
minutes.
Yeah. 10 minutes.
These two are left.
I kind of want to get this
Wait, where did I drop the
Dang it?
Oh, the sentinel is here.
That thing is the sentinel, right?
I do want to fight it.
Oh my god. So, how many keys am I
getting today?
Uh,
should I fight it?
I do need the sentimental call though.
There we go.
I'm over encumbered.
I'll try my luck to survive.
Get home safe.
Guess I needed this.
What do I replace? Uh
is that it?
I can take the hatch.
>> I'll take the hatch.
I'll do get down
here.
Okay, this
would be my first time taking a hatch
from them.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Okay, bye-bye.
Oh my god, we got a good loot.
We got good loot.
We got good loot, ladies and gentlemen.
89. That's the highest ever I got.
Oh my god.
Oh, crazy
man.
Uh, take this this.
So, I did say that I wanted to like save
up some of these uh shrinking goods. No.
All right. I did say that. So, I'm going
to do that actually.
save some of these trinkets out
and then
I I can always sell the duck cuz we have
a one stack of ducks, right? So, I'll
keep it saved over here. Then I'll keep
on
getting more stuff. And yeah, so
basically it didn't make much since I'm
doing like like that.
Uh that's okay.
I got a rattler.
Bastian's house
surveyor.
Wait, what?
Wait, I never upgraded this leaper. Oh,
I need the leaper. What?
I need the
motor.
I need one more terminal.
Uh
mustache is looking too.
Uh I need a
Shall we go kill some?
I want to go kill some.
I do want to go kill some.
Uh
stuff.
Okay. What do I need again? Um
surve. Okay. Sentinel fire and core. I
need two more
uh water. No.
I was thinking maybe I'll
go kill some.
I have three wolf packs. All right. I
can take down one rocketeer, I guess.
But one won't be enough. No.
I would need to kill multiple right for
the
for the trials.
I have to do I have to 4,000
damage.
Isn't it better to buy get the Hulk
cracker and damage our rocketeer?
Rocket. Rocket.
Go kill big robot. Yeah.
Sure.
Yeah, of course you can join. Come in.
Dio.
Yeah. Join in. Join in. How long? I I
have to wrap up though. It's fine. It's
fine. We can come come in. coming in. We
haven't played. Yeah.
Let me come with you.
Uh
okay. Any
There's a blue gate.
I ra is there.
Join in the big come like let's beat up
some big boys.
Okay, let me check my miscellaneous. How
much money can I make from this?
49.
Yeah, take your time. Lordish
66.
Yeah, we can do. Okay. Okay. Okay. We
can do rocket. If if that's the case,
then
yeah, I'll take this. Yeah. Wait, should
I buy the
hullcracker? I don't have the
>> You better have coin raider.
>> I'll be broke.
>> You're blocking the door. No.
Don't mind me. I'm just going to buy one
energy club. Okay. Just wanted to test.
You sell it for 1k.
That's so That is so cheap. But I know
that is so low.
Uh
1.5.
>> Hey, what can I get you?
Um,
our commotion core. I need this.
every
What do I need for this again? Caution
core and
There's that. I'll track both of them so
I can like not keep them crafted up and
showstopper.
Showstopper [cough and clears throat]
as well.
Hello Zawa.
Oh, wait. I'll call
I'll call you. Wait, do I have Discord?
Okay, I have.
Hi, let me call you.
Uh
what?
>> Ah hello.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Yes.
>> Okay, let's do the rocket here at blue
gate. Uh,
all you need to do it's an anvil and let
it target you and I'll do the rest.
>> Anvil.
>> I'll try crazy.
>> Just try to shoot it.
>> Let it target you.
>> What gun are you using?
>> A deadline [laughter] and a
>> You get me? Do you get me?
>> Yes.
>> Hold on. Need to charge my
>> Yeah.
Uh,
take care. Good night.
Oh,
are you sleeping early?
>> Not early, but it's late for you. No.
So,
>> three going to be three.
>> Just bring one gun. Yeah, just bring one
gun.
>> One gun. Okay. [sighs]
Okay, this should be quick. I bring two
in case someone want to kill us.
[laughter]
>> Oh my god. Don't say it like that. Okay.
Wait. Should I take the wolf pack?
>> No, I think we're fine. But I think you
should put in a safe pocket just in case
I [\h__\h] up.
>> Just in case. [laughter]
Cuz I [\h__\h] up once and I lost like a
snap hook.
>> No.
Okay, I have my
my secret weapon here.
>> Are you taking in
I have a medium shield?
>> Why you medium?
>> It's not that crazy. Come on, Chuck.
>> I've been using light for whatever.
>> Come on.
It's not that hard to create a to to
craft a medium shield. Just a processor
and the battery. No, wait. Is it? No. Is
it the uh was it
>> the circuitry? Arc circuitry and the
battery.
>> That is true.
>> Not that hard. [laughter]
>> Mine still.
>> What? You fear you're going to lost it.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, come on. That's the point of this
game. Do not fear of losing thing.
>> Oh, that is true. Yes. Mhm.
Hello, Zappy. Welcome.
How much money space coins do you have
right now?
>> I have 60k because I uh had to uh reset
my uh my skill tree to get the security
breach. I didn't know there's a 75 level
like cap.
>> Yeah, that's why expedition. [laughter]
>> Ah, god damn it. Okay. Wait, so when you
do expedition, do you
>> gain extra permanently.
[laughter]
>> Okay.
>> Collab stream. No, we just playing
together. Can call it hanging out and
chilling.
Yes.
>> How did it reach 75?
>> What?
>> How did you even reach level 75? How
much did you grind the
>> Oh, a lot.
>> I just grind. I fight a lot of matriarch
and queen
>> kill a bunch of people too.
>> Three matriarch matches and I didn't get
anything.
>> Oh, you have to be you have to be
skilled at rat.
>> Uh I sold like tons of matriarch uh core
already. The reactor. I sold like bunch
of them.
You're crazy.
>> Cuz I don't know what to use for cuz I
don't have the Aelion.
>> Guys, I'm going to bring the Trailblazer
just in case.
>> Mhm. Or did you get the Trailblazer
blueprint?
>> Uh, I did. Yeah.
>> Where did you find that?
>> I don't know.
That's the point. I don't know.
I got like I think I have the blueprint
for most of the gun now except for the
legendary.
>> Yeah, I think I have Yeah, I have
blueprint for all the gun now. Except
for the legendary. I have anvil.
Let me see. Oh my god. Toro, Vantor,
Renegade, Osprey, Tempest, Bobcat.
Goddamn.
>> Just need a volcano.
>> Why you got bobcat, bro?
Yeah. Crazy. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Not long ago, I got a blueprint for the
uh the fee, too.
>> I craft another dead line.
>> Oh, come on. I'm out of oil.
>> How's this dash situation looking?
>> Uh quite okay. I keep spending stuff and
it's keep
you know have space in my inventory
>> which is fine.
>> What what about the expedition? How far
have you reached?
>> Only second page. [laughter]
>> I didn't pay attention to it much.
>> So
>> yeah,
>> let me see. Let me see. What do I need?
expedition.
Need durable class. I need wires.
Need cooling fan.
>> Okay, sounds good. All right, let's go.
Uh, yeah.
Wait, hold on.
>> Hold on.
>> Need to show
>> where which map do you want? If we wait
like 50 seconds, it'll gonna switch.
>> Let's just do blue gate. Blue gate on uh
night raid.
>> Okay,
let's go.
Ah, wait. I canceled it. Sorry. Ah, get
in. Get in. Okay.
Will we get it?
Isn't it a bit ski if the if the
What if we don't get blue
night raid?
>> What? What you What do you mean?
>> Like it's going to switch out now in a
few seconds.
>> Yeah. Yeah, but you still get it.
>> Oh, we do get it. Oh, yeah. We got it.
That is all
trapeteers.
No one. There should be one around the
village.
>> I have a secret weapon for avoid
shooting.
>> I swear no one going to shoot you most
of the time if you play the flute.
>> Wait, who's is it you? The flute.
Yeah.
Oh, snitches. That's my fleet.
[laughter]
>> No one going to shoot you with this. I
swear. No one going to kill a guy with a
flute. That's the secret strat.
Wait, how do you craft the flute?
>> I don't know. You cannot. I think you
only can find it.
>> Ah,
that's a bombader.
>> Let's go this way.
It's
>> a leaper.
>> They need to do something with the
leaper and the rocketeer
cuz their reactor doesn't doesn't do
anything.
>> The leaper recover for the expedition.
>> Really? Oh well, I have like tons of
them. How many do you need?
Uh,
I actually forgot.
We need like
>> just four.
Yeah, four or something. Some some Yeah,
four or something. Yeah,
four or six. Not sure. Wait, that was
the coal snap event.
That was four, right? No, wait. No, no,
no. You didn't have to do that. Oh,
never mind.
>> Oh.
>> Uh,
>> is there a rocketeer?
There has to be.
>> A lot of
>> there.
Kill this.
>> A lot of
>> ah [\h__\h]
>> All right.
>> You drug.
>> Welcome.
>> Okay. Get a house. Find a house and
hide. There's also a bombader around
here.
>> Oh, wait. Should we use this in that
building?
>> Uh, there's a bombader over there, I
think, cuz there are two spotter.
>> Hello. Hello. Hello.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
this team here.
>> Don't shoot.
[laughter]
>> [\h__\h]
they they chill. They chill.
Okay, let's lure the ruger. Just find a
house first.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, where is he? Where's that thing?
>> Is that him?
>> Oh my god. Oh, hornet. I need a hornet,
too. I haven't finished the hornet.
>> I have me, too.
>> You can share the score, by the way, if
you don't know.
>> It's on me. It's on me. It's on me. I'm
going to run.
>> Get Get in here. Get in here. Get in
here.
Holy [\h__\h] Okay.
>> Oh my.
>> Uh, get a house. Get a house.
Let's go. Uh, down here,
man.
Okay,
>> I need I needed this kit. Oh, hello.
>> Chill, chill, chill. We're doing the
rocket here.
>> Okay, come on. Come that.
>> Hold on. Let me kill the hornet.
Come on.
>> Okay.
>> Ow. Come on. I'm going to start
damaging.
Okay.
>> Okay. Shoot it. Start. Shoot it. Let it
aggro. You
let me try to snitch it somewhere. Go
behind it.
Oh, there's so many [\h__\h] robots
around here. Jesus. There's snitcher on
you, too.
[\h__\h] that hell.
Oh, is it it's a plus spotter spotter?
>> Oh, it spotted you.
>> Oh, the womber is nearby.
>> Ah, [\h__\h] the woo.
>> I did not take any defense, by the way.
Don't die. Okay.
>> Oh my god. Hold on.
>> Okay, I damaged one.
>> Jesus Christ.
I damaged one of the wings of the horn.
Uh the wings.
>> Yeah. Good, good, good. Do you know if
uh share the um the score?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> D. Yeah,
>> that's good. Okay, let me try doing
something. I needed to stun it somehow.
At the wing. At the wing. Right. Shoot
at the wing.
Okay. Hold on.
Stand. Stand. Stand. Stand. Stand.
Stand. Stop. Oh, it's dead.
>> Where?
>> Um.
>> What?
>> What? [laughter] Okay. We need one more.
We need one more.
>> One more. Oh, come on.
[laughter and gasps] I just stunned it.
Fell to death,
bro. It's so funny.
My god, my aim. Hello. Hello.
Oh my god, my aim. No one see that.
No one freaking see that.
Let's chill.
>> I want ow you one.
How much score we have now? Oh, halfway.
Okay.
Uh, the bombader. Oh, Sentinel.
>> Where?
>> Holy [\h__\h] There's
>> Sentinel.
>> Oh, we need I needed that.
>> But but there's a bombarder over there,
too. Job. Careful.
There's a bombarder right below it.
I don't think you can do
>> one should be um
>> I don't know. I don't know where
>> I mean you can.
>> That's the only one.
>> Oh, it's targeting someone. It's
targeting you.
>> Me? No, not me. Someone
>> might be busy lag anyway.
Oh my god.
>> Try to kill as much as hornets as we
can. Okay, we can finish this off.
>> Uh yeah.
I'll try to look for the rocketeer up
here.
Let me see.
>> I should have gotten more ammo.
Heavy ammo.
Oh no.
Ah,
nice.
What is that
>> over there?
>> So, was
try to find a rocketeer
>> by that building.
>> Uh, please don't be far away. I mean,
technically, we can just wait here until
the rocketeer respawn. Should be like 8
minutes or something.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
No, no, there should be more rocketeers,
though.
Yeah,
but they're quite hard to find since
they don't have like a big light like
all the other drones.
>> What is this?
>> Leaper. The ruined home.
>> Leaper.
That you
>> I'm over here.
So many spotters. Wait, there's another
rock mater.
Jesus, why are there so many bomb?
>> Jesus.
>> Someone is someone extracted.
>> Uh yeah, there's a guy.
Play a fleet to him.
>> I think I found one.
So technically we need to kill two more
rocketers.
>> So three in total I guess.
Crazy.
>> Holy [\h__\h]
>> Someone's dying.
Sentinel Raiders refuge.
>> Wasp over there.
>> Wasp.
>> Should we?
Okay, let me change my graphic settings
so I can see farther.
>> I'm going to blow up your freaking
stream, Jock.
>> [laughter]
>> Stop.
>> How come there's only one?
>> Where?
>> Or should we just kill all the hornets
at least and extract? Maybe.
>> But that's the problem. There's no
hornet around.
H. Oh, my gun is about to break. No.
>> Oh, wait. Wait. Something spawn.
Where is it? Where is that? What's
spawn? What just spawn?
Uh, not you. Where are you?
>> Snitch.
Okay, let me kill this snitch first.
>> Oh, nearby.
>> Oh [\h__\h] there's two wasp.
Wait, what is going up?
>> Why is the snitch going up?
>> What the [\h__\h] Someone God damn this
thing.
Do you have a bandages?
>> Uh yeah. Take this.
Take it. Take it. Take it.
>> Listen.
>> You can you can heal me.
>> Rocketeer. Where are you? Where are you?
Rocketeer.
Where are you?
>> Should we reset? Maybe
>> I still got bunch of time.
>> Oh no, someone's dead.
>> Someone died.
>> Someone's dead. Yeah.
>> Why did I lose
[laughter]
snitches? Oh my god. Down there. One,
two, three, four, six drones. Oh my god.
I think we should reset.
Wait, what's that?
>> Hornet.
>> Is that a player?
>> Oh, yeah. Don't shoot at the player. It
will send you to a cursy lobby, I think.
>> Uh, Hornet coming.
>> Oh, come on. Oh, come on. Oh, come on.
How much is it? Okay, we are half one
star in another spawn.
>> We are watch
durability 10 out of 100. Holy.
>> Do you recycle
the
>> No, just repair. Ah,
>> I upgraded and just upgrade the gun.
You don't upgrade the gun.
>> I know.
>> Why don't you upgrade the gun? It just
It's a lot of difference.
>> Okay.
Yeah, I really need to do that.
>> Ah, here.
>> Okay,
>> so I did get spawned.
>> I only have 17.
>> Oh Jesus, the bird. The bird just
scattered [\h__\h] out of me.
>> Uh,
>> okay. Same thing. Let it target you. Ah.
Ow.
>> Where is it?
Uh, a west.
Ah,
>> see it? Do you see it?
>> Where is it? The [\h__\h]
>> Where is it?
>> Where the hell?
Rocket. Oh, over there.
>> Okay, I only have like 18 bullets.
Make this quick. Okay,
>> maybe this building.
Okay, let me lure it first. Oh my god,
it's close. Uh, hold on, hold on, hold
on. Can we go up high and shoot it?
Going to go on top of the roof first. Is
there like a window on the roof or
something?
>> Uh, it's this building.
>> Oh my god, I broke my ankles again.
>> Snitch on top again.
Try to shoot at the rocketeer once
and come to me.
>> Okay, hold on. It's coming this way. Uh,
where is it? The [\h__\h]
>> Wait, this position is bad. Uh,
which room
did we
>> I shot it.
>> Okay, this does not have a roof. Ah,
>> just stand in the building, I would say.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. Shoot it. Can you shoot it? It's
coming to me.
>> Where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
Mark.
>> Uh, I see it.
>> Like on top of my head. You see it?
>> Oh, come on. There's a wasp.
>> I'm dead. I'm dead. Oh, you're not dead.
Careful.
I couldn't move my pieces as I show it.
>> Yeah, find a better spot outside. Let it
target me.
>> Okay, it's over here.
>> Okay.
>> Come on. Come to puppy.
Come on. Come on.
Okay, just shoot one. Don't Yeah, just
let it target you and hide somewhere.
I needed to stand still.
I got to be more careful.
Oh [\h__\h] I missed.
Is it stun? It's not done. Oh wait,
that's my chance. Oh. Oh, come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Where is
it?
>> Oh, I did not see it hit me like that.
Oh,
>> plant now. Now, now, now. I got it. Got
it. I got it.
>> Oh, nice.
>> It's dead. It's dead. I'm dead, too.
There you go, Jock. And you revived me
real quick. Where? Where? Where?
Where are you?
>> I'm here. I'm here.
I'm in the middle of the road.
>> Oh my god.
>> There you go.
>> Oh, where did you do it? How did you
actually do it?
>> Oh, just stun the drone. And when when
it's when the rocketeer is done, it's
going to go down, right? It's going to
fly down to the ground. And then I just
climb up
>> and shoot it and put a dead line on it.
Actually put a deadline. Yeah.
>> Ah
>> yeah.
Just do quick or else it's going to fly
up and then drop you down. That's what
happened to me before.
>> 10 minutes to get out of there. I repeat
today or
>> get the hell out of here.
>> Finish it. Let's Let's leave. Let's
leave actually.
obviously.
>> Oh my god, it's so far away.
>> Uh, we're fine.
>> We progressed a lot.
>> How much point we have?
>> Have we finished it?
>> Yeah,
just one. Just one deadline. That's how
I did the Bastion last week, too. Just
put the deadline behind it. Just one
deadline and I got the whole whole
>> sorry full score.
>> Nice.
>> How much we have for hornet? Uh halfway.
>> Let's do the hornet on the on our way
back. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Alex let's reach the place then we
get
>> I mean it's close
>> is it
>> is it close
>> oh wait that's my ping sorry that's my p
that's my ping
>> yeah where is it ah this way right
[sighs]
is my weapon oh three okay my weapon is
going to break.
>> It's all right.
>> Die, Jo.
If we're friendly, they friendly.
I just don't want to don't want to die
and lose the progress.
>> Is it leaper?
>> Is this a leaper? Oh god.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's a leaper sound.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Don't say don't shoot. Play the flute.
>> Never say don't shoot. Just play the
flute.
No one No one going to kill you. No one
going to kill a guy with a flute.
>> Where Where are you?
>> I'm behind you.
kind of want to stay a little bit for
the hornet.
>> Yeah,
>> yeah, we can just stay.
>> Hello, Raider.
>> Hello.
>> Hey, don't shoot. Thanks.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Hello, people.
Uh, jock on your hat. Oh, damn. Okay.
Okay. Let's just stay there. Let's just
stay here
and try to find hornet. What is that?
>> Hey. Hello.
>> Wasp. Wasp.
>> There's a leaper right on my feet.
>> Okay. I have a a wolf pack. Should we
kill it?
>> Nah, just to be safe. I don't think we
should.
>> I'll save it. Yeah,
>> just a leaper anyway.
>> Let's make sure the leap.
>> I can kill it with one true blazer. I
think
>> want to go for it. [laughter]
>> Wait, no. Wait, don't don't. It will
jump though when you shoot at it
>> or when
>> Yeah. I want to go for it.
>> Yeah. TV really want to sacrifice.
There's only five minutes.
>> What you scared? Huh? Are you scared?
[laughter]
>> There's no hornet. There's only wasp.
>> Oh my god. And then let the sporters see
you and then let it call the uh hornet.
>> Spoiler only call
>> it. It will give you the
>> hornet.
>> Yeah.
Not spoiler. Uh snitch. I feel like feel
like snitch, right?
>> Yeah, snitch.
Is that it?
>> Oh, got a vinator. What the hell?
>> Let's go home.
I don't see any points.
>> Want to kill one more rocketeer?
>> No.
>> Raiders areteer
around us. There's one. Oh,
>> there's always Pilgrim Peak which has a
lot of rocket spawn.
>> I got to shoot it. [laughter]
>> Oh my god.
>> Are you going to shoot it?
>> Uh when the uh the thing opened. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
Another one. Okay. You shoot that one.
I'll shoot the one behind us.
>> All right. All right. All right. Three,
two.
>> Oh [\h__\h] Jock. Uh, there's one really
close to us. [laughter]
>> I shot it. I shot it. Just shot it. Run.
>> We shot it again.
Woo.
Wait. Quick, quick.
>> Come, come, go, go, go, go, go.
Okay.
Oh my god, that scared me.
Oh boy.
>> Finally, we finished it.
>> See what I got.
>> Me too.
Blower grenade. I got
>> simple gunpow.
Oh, I got a a second blueprint.
>> Oh, come on.
>> Oh, let's go. I got um a stock pad at
stock.
>> I already got a blueprint for it. Come
on.
>> So, I heard you can Do you know how to
make a new account
in Arc? Do I have to buy a new game?
Yeah.
>> What? Really?
>> Yeah. What do you want to transfer your
stuff?
>> Yeah, I wanted to
>> cheeky bastard. [laughter]
>> Oh, imagine that would be so nice. No.
>> Oh my god.
Wait, do you do you want the survivor?
>> No, I know. I have it already. A
[laughter]
okay. What else?
Trader raider. Uh the trial
hornet pops
the lever caribou. Okay.
What's the map right now?
I'm going to see the map.
We're not able to see the map.
>> Yeah, only you can see the map, I think.
>> Uh I thought
Huh. Okay, wait.
>> Yeah, only you like the uh the what do
you call it? The lobby owner.
>> Uh okay, wait one second.
Do you what do you recycle normally
>> a lot?
Keep the stuff that you can use to craft
>> like the shredder JRO. I can just
recycle it cuz it's not used for
anything now. I think I think
>> Shredder JRO is needed for the second
>> expedition.
>> Yeah, we are on the first expedition,
right?
>> Got it. They said they're going to
revamp the expedition thingy.
>> Stella want this night raid is there.
>> Oh boy. That's going to be a whole uh
>> our damn battlegrounds. Wait, Stella
will be easier to finish the that
rolling ball thingy, right?
>> Yeah.
>> I want to go.
Let me upgrade my gun.
>> Oh, I have to upgrade the gun. I forgot.
Uh, [sighs] handwell.
>> Where's my
I don't have resources. Oh, never mind.
Mechanical components.
How do you get mechanical components?
Oh.
It's that easy.
Uh, gun
level up
and I got
upgraded to level four. Imagine
I die. I'll cry. [laughter]
Okay. Uh, what argument are you taking?
>> I'm taking
survivor.
>> Are you actually taking? Okay.
>> You know what? Checking combat.
Combat two.
I'll take combat one.
I'm scared.
Like I'll take the defa vote this time.
Did you get the defa blueprint?
>> Yeah, I did.
>> Wow.
Nice. Nice.
Okay. somewhere.
Get some bandage and I have to craft,
you know, buy some
shield.
>> Come on in, Raider. I've got the good
stuff ready.
>> You're making me look good here. Keep it
up.
>> Okay, let's go.
>> So, we're going Stella, right?
>> Stella or damn. Yeah, Stella.
>> Let's do Stella.
>> Yep. Let's go. Bring my
One sec. One sec.
Uh, where's my ammo?
>> There we go.
>> What do you get after re uh upgrading
med medicine lab? Did you finish the arc
ser uh surveyor?
medicine and what
>> did you upgrade your lab medicine
medical lab to level three?
>> Uh yeah, nothing much.
>> Is it purple or blue stuff you unlock?
>> No, I think there's a Vita spray, but
you need a blueprint for that.
>> Ah,
>> I think so.
Okay. Oh [\h__\h] I need shield. Forgot
about that.
recharge.
Let's just bring
that. I'll bring 3D feep.
I don't have metal pods. Oh my god, I'm
broke. Broke.
>> More bandages. is just tell me what you
want.
>> Oh, I'm broke, too. Can't even craft
bandages.
>> Let's go.
>> Oh, you got the Leviathan said no. Nice.
>> Yep.
Forgot
the scope.
Now I'm ready.
I just hope I never tried Stella Montes
duos. Did we ever try it together? I
hope it's not PVP.
It
>> depends. But uh it happens. Yeah,
depends.
I don't want to lose anvil.
>> I got my I got my flute.
[laughter]
>> No one shoot the flute.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh yeah. Uh for trials now you can keep
on going and breaking the record.
>> Uh yeah. Yeah.
>> I saw like someone did like 10k score on
throwing balls at Rocketeer. [laughter]
>> Crazy. Oh my god.
>> That was so funny.
Yeah. Somehow for me somehow I stun the
uh rocketeer and it just flipped.
>> The thing just completely upside down.
Oh, it's going to fly.
>> Yeah.
>> Is the queen and the matriarch
different?
>> How the same?
>> They are.
>> They are different. Matriarch is bigger,
move less, and less attack. And it
summon it mainly summon like the other
guy like Bastion and Bombadier.
The queen has like a lot of stuff
like she has like a laser beam stun
shield.
>> Oh, the thing is
>> uh
machine gun.
>> Do you want to kill this shredder?
>> I can. It's not that hard to kill.
>> Oh god, I just do it.
>> Start the battle.
Just hide behind the wall.
It's going that way.
Hello, good sir. J,
let me go on this side.
Hello.
What the [\h__\h] [laughter]
Mine's so low. I need a higher ground.
>> It's almost dead. There's a pop down
there.
>> Pop.
Come back here.
Okay. Nice. H
>> nice.
>> Is that you?
>> Yeah, that's me.
>> Wait, where is the
He just get one guy roll.
>> Where the hell are that sound coming
from?
>> Is it nearby?
Ah, [\h__\h] hell. Right in front of my
face.
>> Oh no. Hello. How come?
>> Oh, come on. Where the [\h__\h] do these
guys coming from?
[laughter]
I swear this thing is like creeper in
Minecraft.
I see another one.
>> Nice.
>> Okay, we got one star.
Oh my god, purple loot. Okay, I forgot
this is that place where you can get
good stuff.
Oh my god.
Light gun parts.
>> Oh, this is the good place to leave.
>> This is where I got the Alfon blueprint.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Where you got it? You finding a lock
room or just
>> from the
Oh,
got it.
>> Nice.
>> From the what do you call it? Uh
>> medical.
>> Yeah.
No, no, it's from here. I just uh s
breach to this
country room. Oh,
you need a microscope. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I
just breached the breach and search the
server rooms and I um
literally literally just clicked it.
How do we craft sensor? Right.
>> Sensor.
>> Uh hash key just in case. Oh, wait. It's
night raid.
>> It's night raid.
>> Ah,
>> sadly, Jo. Sadly,
>> sadly,
>> I have security breach. Okay, I'll try
to find.
>> Oh,
>> if you see a security breach thing, call
me. I I want
>> I'll let you know.
I see more of the balls.
Okay, I got three from that. So, Oh, we
finished it.
>> What?
>> We finished it
>> already.
>> Oh, go home. D.
>> Wait, wait, wait. No, no, no, no, no.
Let's keep breaking it. We can get the
leaderboard,
>> Jock. Whatever. get killed.
>> Nah,
>> there's still a montest. Do not forget.
This is Stella Montist.
>> I know.
>> You cannot forget. You cannot forget.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Where's everyone?
>> There's no one here. I
>> think they're in like medical or
something.
You're chilling.
Nice.
>> Why didn't you give me notific?
Yeah, it happens.
>> You got shadow ben. That's why.
Security breach, where are you? Ah, hop.
[\h__\h] y see my points. [laughter]
>> Jesus Christ, this little snitch.
>> Just a battery.
>> Ah, fire.
>> Hey, you lead the way. I just follow
you.
What is that?
A supply drop.
>> Oh, wait, wait. Uh, I can't open the
door there. There's a battery here.
>> Oh,
>> which door?
That door.
>> A door.
>> Ah,
a door.
Ah, that's a supply drop. Get it. Oh,
there's
>> someone outside.
There's someone outside behind the door.
Don't shoot.
Oh,
>> hold on. I use my secret.
>> Should we kill?
>> Holy [\h__\h]
There's like two shredder.
>> Want to go?
>> Oh. Oh, yeah. Yeah, sure.
Just a lot of shredder.
>> Uh, close.
>> Oh my god. I almost thought I I died.
>> Don't worry, Jock.
Okay. Shredder coming. Shredder coming.
Get that here.
Coming that way.
>> Got the balls.
>> Left, left, left, left, left, left,
left,
shot.
Ah.
>> Oh my god.
Oh my god.
>> How are you dying?
>> I died.
>> Oh [\h__\h] Oh, the pop.
>> Yeah, the pop. The bop. Yeah.
Oh my god.
Hello. Thank you.
>> Someone outside.
Don't shoot.
>> Hello. Wait. What the [\h__\h]
>> My gun.
>> Wait. Don't shoot us. We're just doing
the challenge. Please.
>> There's a whole team.
>> Quit. Chill. We doing trial. Please,
sir. Wait. Hold on.
>> Let us be. Please. Why?
>> There's two teams.
>> They team up. They [\h__\h] team up. God
damn
>> the challenge, man. Oh, wait. I had so
much epic stuff. No.
>> Oh, well.
>> Wait. Boring up. Who is this guy?
>> I'm telling you. This is Stella Monty.
>> Man, we should have extracted.
>> I'm telling you. Don't forget this is
Stella.
>> They [\h__\h] team up, too. Two team team
up. [\h__\h] hell.
>> [\h__\h] hell.
>> We had 7k on the PS. A
literally wanted to crash out and be
like, "Why are you PvPing? This is
supposed to be a PvE server the match."
[\h__\h] this is teleontism.
There's no there's no mercy.
>> Why?
>> Yeah, depends. Actually, depends.
>> I lost a lot of good stuff.
>> Now you lost like
my anvil.
>> Oh, yeah, the anvil. No,
>> I actually have Wait, did you You lost
the recorder, too. The fluid.
No, my flute.
>> No,
>> I still have a shaker. That's okay.
>> You know what? Let's reload out. Get in
there and kill people.
[laughter]
>> I don't.
>> And the pops.
>> Okay. I'm going to freload out.
>> But mainly we'll do the pops. Yeah.
But if we do kill people, we'll get sent
into a bad lobby though. PVP below me
though.
>> Nah, not really. I kill all the time.
[laughter]
>> Is that who I am? We are getting killed.
Not sure.
>> No,
>> not all the time. I only kill people who
shot me.
>> I forgot the devil said something about
it in the new article or something.
Really?
>> Like how it does the detection?
Like as long as you don't engage in
shooting others, it won't
put you with players with who shoot you
or something. I don't know. Maybe we
were unlucky. Who knows?
But I do want to like PvP and get that
V, you know, how the other streamers are
doing, right?
BP BP and like
do stuff.
>> Oh, I got a rattler. Whatever.
>> Yeah, we got a chair.
>> Toledo is
>> Oh, [\h__\h]
>> There's one shredder. One shredder right
behind that one.
Uh, is there
>> I see some pops.
>> I see a pop, too. All
right, hold on.
Oh my god.
>> Oh my god.
>> Should we kill it?
>> Uh, careful, Jock.
I'm not with
now. We are in the Asian server. That's
why.
Oh, [\h__\h]
>> What happened?
>> I got a deadline blueprint.
>> Wait, what? Really? Yes.
>> Yeah, but I already have it, man.
Could have something better.
Wait, where? Oh, are you paying the
that's why? Okay.
>> Hey, Alex to find something load out,
too.
>> I have a defe shield and smoke bomb.
Okay, smoke bomb
shet
middle part, too.
Right over here.
>> Careful. This might go here.
How many shredder? Jesus Christ.
So many shadows.
Oh, tagging grenade blueprint. Okay,
that's useless.
Hello, M. Welcome.
Wait, where are all we up? Okay.
It's just ammo. There's nothing dead
end. Dead end. Dead end. There's nothing
there.
Go here.
>> Security breach. Where are you?
>> Wait, is that a trend or something?
Hand.
Let's go to the
place where there's pops and stuff.
>> That's going to be a long way.
>> Oh yeah.
>> Uh there's dead end on top. There's dead
end on top.
>> Oh,
>> can only go down.
>> Yeah, let's go down.
>> Shredder. Shredder. Shredder. Shredder
>> people.
>> There's people near. Yeah, there's
people near.
>> Someone already loot this place.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
>> It's looking at you. It's looking at
you. Okay.
Where is it?
>> Where
that? Okay, let's get out of here.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
>> Wrong way. Where are you going?
>> I'll go up.
Okay, it's a friend.
battery.
Uh, my game froze again. No
>> [\h__\h]
>> I got back.
>> Oh, here it is. I heard a radio flare.
>> Oh.
Oh, no.
Water pops.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
>> Uh, over there.
>> Oh, I'll take the
arc also.
Uh, fireball.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Uh, no luck.
Oh, that's uh
uh
>> what
>> there's one down there. Oh, shredder.
>> Yep.
>> Okay, let's get behind something.
>> Hey, that's a friendly fire.
>> No. What? I got
>> Wait,
>> did you show to me?
>> Yeah, I did.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> Oh [\h__\h] See? See this [\h__\h] rat? Come
here. Come here. Come here. Come here.
>> Wait. What?
>> You see this [\h__\h] rat? See?
>> What a [\h__\h] rat.
>> Oh my god.
>> He's so rat.
>> Don't shoot.
>> I'll take the arc. So other people are
there.
So
>> technically we are done with the thingy.
We can keep going to
get
>> maximum.
>> We want shirt.
>> It's so easy in Stella.
Uh
>> I mean Stella is like a close closed
place, right? So that's why
>> it's like a indoor place.
Yep.
>> Don't shoot.
>> It's a lock room.
Oh, this is our key room, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Want to go home?
>> We could or we could just stay longer to
get some more stuff. We're freaking now.
>> You remember what happened last time?
Huh?
>> Yeah. How's that?
Terrible.
>> PvP outside.
>> They're PvPing outside.
>> Wait, who?
>> At the loading bay. Outside. At the
loading bay. I heard PvP.
>> Wait, really? Oh, gun.
>> [\h__\h] third partying them.
>> Uh, I do not know. Oh, come on.
>> Oh my god.
Someone down there. Up there. Down
there. I don't know.
Where is the [\h__\h] Is that you?
>> I'm behind you.
>> Oh, down there. Down there. Down there.
>> Down there.
>> DON'T SHOOT.
I think they're friendly.
>> Did you break your ankle? You did not.
>> No.
Just when you jumped out, just like time
the uh the dodge.
Try to time the Oh [\h__\h] Careful.
Jesus [\h__\h] Are you
uh strider behind you?
>> I died. I died.
>> Oh [\h__\h] You're one HP. Run run run run
run run.
>> Oh my god. Lord only me. [laughter]
What the heck?
I don't have bandages or anything.
It can come to you as long as that
shredder is not
>> Let it go.
>> [\h__\h] that shredder.
>> Where is it? It's right behind the door.
[laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> Wait. Uh,
we need to leave, right? Uh, should we
take this?
>> Uh, yeah, sure.
>> But that's
>> But hold on. Yes.
>> Shutter is going to be a problem.
I can't distract it.
>> Don't die though.
>> Oh, it went away somewhere.
I think you're safe.
Okay, I'm going to search for Arc Arc
lawyers.
Okay, let's go.
>> Oh my god. Holy
>> killed him anyway.
>> Oh, you killed it.
Oh my [\h__\h] Why Why did this pop to
stay still now? Jesus Christ.
>> Oh [\h__\h] Um. Oh lord.
>> Hey, hold on.
>> I thought it was a jumpable window. I I
didn't know I had to.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Let's leave
that way. Seat falls that way.
Someone is stabbed way too.
>> Careful.
>> Don't shoot.
>> I'm going to size this for Aric.
There's one here.
>> Thank you.
That [\h__\h] Oh my god, that thing is
literally guarding the the way.
Yeah.
Try to
>> wait.
>> Oh, damn.
>> When it when it come up here, I going to
try to do this
and run. Wait, balls here. Wait, that's
control room.
Go to the door.
>> Oh my.
>> Wait, not
wait for it to finish shooting.
>> Hide.
I don't think I have enough ammo for
this.
>> Don't mind. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hide, hide, hide, hide.
Okay, I'll go to the door. Come here.
Okay.
>> Yeah.
Okay. Come
>> close it. Nice.
>> Oh my god.
>> Only eight have eight bullets left.
Wait, you want which ammo is it?
>> Medium.
>> Uh,
>> or someone's dead here.
>> Oh,
>> loot. Loot.
>> Well, there's nothing.
>> There's no rats, right?
>> Yeah.
Or probably that's a rat. Yeah. Or a rat
killed him. I don't know.
>> God knows.
Oh, wait. Actually, I will want that. I
want that.
>> You need that? Okay.
>> Uh, you can't here.
>> No, I can craft it. Okay.
>> Oh, you can craft it. Wow. Nice.
>> Okay, just go in. I'll smoke us.
go.
>> Oh my god.
I'm going to throw it at you.
Did you get hurt? No, I threw fire at
you.
Level 46.
>> Okay. What did What did I get?
>> What did I get to?
>> Horizontal grip. Muzzle break three.
>> Blueprint. [\h__\h] flare blueprint.
[laughter]
>> He got a flare blueprint.
Okay, whatever.
>> Nice.
I have a deadline. Okay. Keep this for
one of my folks. You're going to need
it.
>> Okay. Recycle this.
Keep this. Recycle this.
Uh ammo. Ammo. Uh that that uh heavy
shield. Oh, so ster.
Oh, I'm full. Holy.
Ain't no way I'm full.
>> So many people are already in the 3x. I
think they're doing the popping the
thing, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Destroying the popups. Yeah.
800.
>> So for me, damage, the hornets and
carrier boss is left.
Nice.
>> I need everything else.
>> Especially the hornet.
>> But I already got the maps.
>> Let me see.
Let's see other maps.
>> I got next. Uh oh, just the night raid
on city.
>> Bur city. Oh, okay. Bur city is okay.
>> You want to do free or
>> uh let me see.
You know, I'm going to bring my osprey,
some brulet.
Uh, we just going to stand at one place
and try to shoot the
the hornet. That's way easier.
>> Yep.
>> I should bring some mines, too.
>> Okay, let's do that. Uh,
recycle. No, let's just sell it.
So that
I have money so I don't need to craft.
Where's the shield?
He beat the shield.
Okay.
Do you use your weapon mods?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, you do?
>> You don't?
>> No, I just keep it in stash.
>> Bro, come on. You have to use it
at some point.
>> Yeah, at some point. Yeah.
>> Okay. I should bring some mines in case
someone r on us.
>> Oh, yeah.
Uh
we'll we'll try to do the field thingy.
Okay.
>> Field what?
>> Field thingy. Yeah, field depot. If
there is
>> I need you need like what? Three of
them.
>> Need to deliver three in order to finish
it. Yeah. Three. Yeah.
>> I want to use my Osprey, too. But Oh,
you have the blueprint now, so it's easy
for you.
>> I don't have
>> I can craft for you.
>> Sure.
>> Or I could use the toe.
How How do I craft?
>> You'll be the guard. I'll be the
shooter.
[laughter]
>> I need a
>> Anyone comes in our way. Um,
I'll not take the torrent then. Uh, I
could take the pharaoh then maybe just
in case.
Okay, I need a lot of heavy ammo.
Oh god, I have to buy them.
Hold on. RB
brick. Yeah.
>> Yeah, take brick.
I want to grab the survivor, but I don't
know.
Hello.
How was that?
Will I regret that? I don't know.
One stack of these items.
I don't have much.
Okay, let Let me sh
basketball.
Don't fall.
do this
>> and I should regard.
>> Okay.
Uh,
I do need to get
You're not one of my regulars. What do
you need?
>> You paid for it.
Okay.
Arc power. I have to start ordering it
soon.
Arc power shells.
I'm having some lag. Oh. Oh no.
Wow.
Are you sure?
So,
what's the day?
Okay, save this.
My other Discord is getting laggy. Oh
lord.
Oh boy.
>> Do I need anything else? Uh, bandage,
shield. Okay, I'll take
I do want to
>> the kettle maybe. Not sure.
90 100
110 120 120 ammo. Okay. 120 300. Okay.
Shotgun
silencer.
That sounds cool.
A shotgun silencer.
>> Hello.
>> Hi. Welcome back. Welcome back.
>> Yes. Hello.
Should I bring my Tempest?
>> I don't know.
>> Like,
>> wait, what are we doing again? Um,
>> uh, Hornet.
>> Hornet. Yes.
>> What What's the on the map now? Is it
still night and Brew City?
>> One second. Uh,
yeah. Brew City. Night trade. Yep.
>> All right. Okay.
Why is every other event is locked? Like
>> need a timer
switch, you know.
>> No, the time I see the time it's grayed
out though. Why is it?
>> Yeah. I don't know why. I don't know.
>> Wow.
Oh, this Oh, spaceport has matri matri.
>> Matriarch spayport. Okay. Okay. Oh, I'm
down. Oh god.
>> Going to bring uh that that that. Okay,
hold on. Suit up.
[laughter]
>> If you say so.
I am so down.
Okay, let's go.
>> We have to loot so much.
>> Got
to go.
But
>> be careful, though. I got like There's a
lot of rats here, too.
>> Ah, yeah, that's true.
>> So, let's just wait for people to fight
it. If people fight it, then we join. If
no one fight it, we go home.
>> Yeah,
>> I'll create I'll craft a radar hatch
key.
In case no one fight it, then we're just
going to go home safely.
>> Yep.
I feel like I would um the the next um
what do you call? Wait, if the exp if
the wipe is on February.
Oh, wait. That means only a few days
left. Few weeks left.
Oh my god.
Wait. 38 days. Wait.
Uh
15. 1 2 3 4 5 6 No. 7 7 14 15 16 17.
19 2023
638.
Oh, February 21st it the wipe is
happening.
>> Okay.
>> 21st or 20th. Oh, the window opens.
Okay. We have 5 days now. So, Oh, okay.
Not a lot of time.
I'm bringing my tempest.
>> The thing is you have to you have to
dump
1 mil of items worth of item.
>> Mhm.
>> And then you have to get 5 mil of money.
Ah, so much stuff.
>> Yeah, let's go.
Heal, shield. What else? Probably that's
enough.
>> Let's go.
>> Oh, nice.
What trial rank did you get? Right
now I am
white card one.
What? Wild card one. Oh, I'm wild card
three.
>> Where
Don't you think the barricade kit is
really good?
>> The what?
>> The barricade
kit.
>> Uh, depend. That thing is very
situational. I never used it. So,
how's it go?
Oh, threshers
near
the sound of my Tempest.
>> And always keep a close eye on her
children.
>> Oh, yeah. But
>> I'm bringing Tempest and Cracker.
>> Nice. Imagine I don't want to say, but
imagine they'll add weapon skins.
No, no,
>> I mean they can. It doesn't really
affect anything. Just
>> Yeah,
>> hopefully.
>> I will even see the weapon skin. I
wonder.
>> Do you want to let the snitch call the
hornet?
>> No, we don't get much point going like
normal.
Why the [\h__\h] is it so tanky?
Oh my god.
Oh, that bullet.
[laughter]
The thing should be at the launch tower.
towers.
>> Should wait a little bit. See if anyone
shooting.
>> My game is lagging again. Oh, people
>> PvP.
>> Wait, actually, no.
>> Oh, wait. No, no, no, no, no. I just
heard a radar flare. [\h__\h]
Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's
start it.
>> It is time.
>> Come on. Shoot more.
>> Why they're not shooting?
>> Shoot more.
All right, we can We need to find a
spot. I don't want to go there cuz there
will be a lot of people.
>> There will be a lot of people at the
launch tower.
>> Oh, they're doing the gas. Oh, wait. No.
Matrix does the gas thing, right?
>> Yeah.
Watch this.
Ow.
>> Wait. Do you have a skill point
>> or what?
>> Wait. How do you roll?
Oh, alt.
>> Okay. I heard a trick. If you're out of
stamina and you roll
>> ah that one
>> to the edge.
[\h__\h] there's a snitcher behind me.
>> Got a wasp overhead.
>> There's a wasp.
>> God damn it. Okay.
I'm going in.
>> Wait, wait. Chill, chill, chill, chill,
chill. We're just doing matriarch.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Don't shoot.
>> Hey, don't shoot. Don't shoot.
>> Wait, he's actually killing.
>> Yeah, they're killing.
>> Don't shoot.
Oh [\h__\h]
>> Hey, don't shoot. We're just doing the
matriarch. Please don't kill.
>> Uh,
should we?
>> No, just
>> uh leave
home.
>> I have the hatch key. Ping me the hatch
key near someone.
>> Uh, hatch is not nearby.
No, we're that
>> hatch is here, but that's far away.
>> Let's just go here.
>> What's wrong with these people? What's
wrong with [\h__\h] Asian server? My god.
>> I I I thought
>> was the most toxic.
>> NA server is normal.
>> Asian server is like freaking sweatiest
people.
They always shoot on sight.
>> You want to reset or go back?
>> I mean, they're are fighting.
>> Up to you.
>> We can go. Want to go? Still want to go.
They're still fighting.
>> Uh, look, look on the left. Okay, just
keep an eye.
There was two teams, too.
>> I don't get why. Like, what were you
doing earlier?
>> I just running.
They shoot on sight. This freaking view.
Alex,
>> thank god I got a smoke bomb. Holy [\h__\h]
>> Hold on.
>> There we go.
My god.
>> Is it because of your uh gun? They're
like, "Oh yeah, I want it."
They can't see from afar.
>> They can get so far away.
>> Probably.
>> Yeah.
>> I find a Brian of Ventor. God damn.
Freddy Fazd.
Oh, these people are so lame.
Okay, let's get rid of this. Going to
bring uh
o
there.
Uh yeah.
>> Or you just want to do nitrate?
>> Nah, I want to kill matriarch.
>> Okay. Okay, let's go.
That's how we get friendly people.
goes without saying, "Do not hands
unless
is not trust.
Oh boy.
All right, cool.
The charger.
Wait.
What time is it for you, Bacon?
Uh,
>> 2:30. 2:30 p.m.
>> Ah, did you had your lunch?
>> Yes. Brunch.
>> Yes, brunch.
Oh, you already loaded quickly. I'm
Wait, what? I was late.
I'm having 10 FBS. No wonder. [laughter]
>> Okay, an FPS. Okay, we're close. Hello.
Hello. Where's
>> Matriarch?
>> I'll need someone to chuck them at.
>> Uh, you can started it.
We can go to launch tower first. Loot
there. There's a lot of good stuff up
there.
>> Yeah.
[\h__\h]
>> I don't have a PvP gun. Really quite
useless.
I only have the osprey and whole
cracker.
The top
Oh, you can't go like this. Oh.
>> Oh, you can.
Oh, you can't.
Oh, you can. Yeah.
Is there anyone up there? Oh, [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] Holy [\h__\h]
>> What happened? Oh, no. No.
What the [\h__\h] happened to you?
>> You're scared of me. So I turned down.
>> What do you mean that scared you?
>> Is there [laughter]
is that [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I was
like, wait, is there a people fighting?
>> No. I got a tick on my face at the same
time there's a fireball and then a pop
coming out at me.
>> Never mind.
>> Okay. [\h__\h] I have this gun. Cannot
fight close range. You go up first.
There should be a pop there.
>> Oh, wait.
>> Oh, someone call the uh
>> start it.
You know what? I'm going to fight it.
Hello.
Ah, my game froze. No.
>> Oh no. Oh no. Jock. Jock. Jock.
Don't die.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
>> Are you good up there?
>> Uh, the
spider.
My god, that [\h__\h] thing.
>> Thank you.
>> Loot.
>> Oh my god, this freaking thing.
>> Where are you?
Should I chop that?
>> Oh, I got it.
>> There you go.
Why no one coming to find the
>> Wait, what? Oh,
>> just a thing. Flare flare flare
blueprint.
>> I'll take that.
>> No one's fighting it. Come on, guys.
Stop being boring.
Feel like people are going to PVP soon.
My game is freezing here and there.
[laughter]
>> Where is it?
>> It's over there. Oh, that big spider.
>> Let me find a spot first.
The good spot is under underneath,
right?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
Damn. Wait. Do you have the deadline?
>> Nope.
Ah.
I don't care.
Look at that thing. Oh my god.
>> My textures are not loaded.
>> [\h__\h]
Oh, [\h__\h] It's the gas.
>> I got the fuse grenade.
>> Oh, hello. Oh, that's you.
That's someone else.
>> Oh my
Oh, what the [\h__\h] Did he just dodge?
He just [\h__\h] dodged my What?
>> That's so weird. I see other people
fighting or just us.
>> That's me, I think. Yeah, just me.
Leaper right there. Hello, Leaper.
Oh, it's stuck. Look, it's stuck. Oh,
nice.
A hornet. Hornet.
Whoa. It's not dead.
Okay.
>> Are these not lootable? It's not.
What the [\h__\h]
>> Ow.
Got you. Jesus.
Where is it?
>> It's on the other side, I believe.
>> Why? No one is fighting. What the [\h__\h]
Shut the [\h__\h]
Oh my god.
I run
almost dead.
Nice.
At least we can all go home with this.
Wait, where's the matriarch though?
>> All the way there.
>> Where?
>> Oh, they're fighting it. Some people was
fighting it.
>> Oh.
Oh no, that's a bastion sound. Never
mind. There's somebody over there.
>> Wait, is people fighting or?
Uh,
>> some of them is fighting the bastion.
There's a sound bastion sound over
there. Well,
>> then we can go there.
>> Yeah. Oh my god. See rocketeer
>> leaper and bombadier.
>> We want to go there.
>> [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] They saw us.
>> Oh my.
Rocketeer is coming.
>> I forgot it can send missiles like
nothing.
Are you calling the rocket here? Yeah,
I'm shooting it.
How come it's so tanky?
>> I think it's a sh it's shields. Uh
>> it's coming. It's coming.
>> I want to go there.
>> It's coming.
>> What?
>> Where are you? It's on me.
What the [\h__\h] How did I miss?
>> Oh, you're killing the rocket. Okay,
okay, okay, okay. Then I'll Yeah, I also
need the rocketeer this thing.
>> Oh, missed again.
>> [\h__\h] was that tick?
>> Stupid tick. I swear to God, I hate the
[\h__\h]
Where is it? Where's that stupid tick?
Thank you.
Careful.
Oh, nice.
>> Oh my god, the matriarch is here.
>> [\h__\h] I missed.
>> Distractor, distractor, distractor,
distractor.
Oh, one piece down.
[\h__\h] the shield.
Oh, the bombader.
Oh my god, I'm there.
For Jo. They're shooting, aiming at you.
Run, run, run, run, run. Holy [\h__\h] that
bombader is crazy.
>> Oh my god.
>> Someone thing with it.
Please.
Okay, that thing is coming here. Uh,
>> it's right outside.
Are you are we sure we can beat it?
>> Shoot this yellow thing on this line.
>> Ah, that one.
>> Oh, nice.
I don't have a deadline. That sucks.
Ow.
>> Okay. My whole cracker is out of
>> uh there's someone speaking. Tell them
not to shoot.
>> Hello. Hello.
>> Is that Japanese?
>> Yeah.
>> I heard Japanese.
>> Oh my god.
>> Am I Am I crazy? I don't think I'm
crazy. [laughter]
>> I think they are Japanese.
and we go the other way.
>> Oh my god. Come on this people, do
something.
>> I'm out of heels.
>> Holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
>> Let me find another spot.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> Do something. There's like six people
around here.
All of them. He's hiding.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. I need I need to kill that
freaking bombader. Where is it?
That thing is such a pain in the ass.
Okay, here.
Got to go kill it.
>> Ah, I died. Wait, wait. Try come to me.
>> Are you dead?
>> Anyone?
Ah,
>> he's from me.
>> Okay, never mind.
There's the leg part.
[screaming]
>> Oh, it's dead.
>> Oh,
>> no. It's not dead. Someone put a
deadline.
>> Oh, actually.
No, it's not dead.
>> Oh [\h__\h]
>> I got to go deal with the bombader. I'm
going to deal with the bombader.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> That thing is so annoying.
>> Wait,
I have this weird feeling.
>> Wait, what? Where? Why are you so out
far?
I have this weird feeling they will
steal our stuff.
Why?
Okay.
Wait, why are you so far out of here?
>> I'm dealing with the bombader. That's
why
>> I got to come back. Oh my god. It's up
over here.
It's on me.
What can I do with you?
>> Let's try this
first.
>> What are they fighting?
>> Oh my Oh, I died again.
>> Oh, come on. I'm so far away. I'm
dealing with this moment here. Try to
stand still. You have a survivor, right?
>> No, I don't.
>> Oh [\h__\h]
>> Oh, someone actually revived me.
>> Thank you.
>> Huh?
>> Oh, my shield broke. Uh, wait. I have a
different extra.
It has a homing.
I think it's a homing.
Oh, yeah. Bacon. Shoot it from here.
Shooting. Shoot it from your place.
>> Also, it's time for us to go to
>> Is the mat truck dead?
>> Nope.
Come to the ma.
>> It's a bombader. Hold on.
>> You're a bombader. Oh my god. Leaper.
Holy,
>> I'm dead. [laughter]
>> Why?
>> I don't have time.
>> We have the survivor, right? Please tell
me.
>> Yeah, I'm survivor.
>> Okay, I have survivor.
>> Slowly crawl. Take your time. Chill and
crawl us to us.
>> But you're almost dead. [\h__\h]
>> Wow. I died. Please don't tell. I'm
dying. I'm dead. Before
you're almost dead, can you ping the
nearest hatch key place?
>> The nearest before you're dead.
>> Okay. Where are you again?
Uh hatch key is here.
>> Oh, right over there. Okay. I'm so
close.
Wait, are you actually extracting
leaving without me?
>> I'll go there and meet you there just to
be safe.
>> Yeah. Orbiter is on route. Safe window
is closing. You have 10 minutes to
return to Spata. I repeat, in 10
minutes.
>> Okay, I already got one reactor.
>> Oh,
>> [\h__\h] It almost dead. Two shot and it's
dead.
There's a rocketeer in my head, too.
Here we go. Just take your time.
You can go around it.
Go the long way.
>> Why?
>> Oh [\h__\h]
Oh no.
Are you dead?
>> I died.
>> Oh,
you're not going to defeat anyone near
you.
>> I don't think
>> that's why you need a medium shield.
>> I don't think these guys have defib.
[\h__\h]
>> [\h__\h] indeed.
>> Oh yes. Oh my god. [laughter] Oh my god.
Oh my god.
Oh my god. Snail of the century.
Don't engage. You don't have nothing.
>> I am.
>> Go the back door.
Oh, it's dead.
>> Someone's dead.
>> It's not. Wait, did not die.
>> Wait, don't die.
>> Someone dead.
What? You Oh my god. You want to loot?
>> Wait, he's looting you or something.
What? No,
>> no, no. I said you want to wait and
loot. It's almost dead. technically.
Okay, come try revive me. I can kill
this thing in in an instant.
>> He's almost going to die.
>> Yeah,
>> I I feel bad. The guy's teammate. Okay,
he's alive.
>> He you they use their revive on me.
[laughter]
>> Well, you don't need a defeat to revive
teammate.
I have a weird feeling someone
accidentally mistakenly shot some
another player. Thankfully they are not
PvPing.
No one's shooting it. God damn.
>> You try to come go this way. Like go
this way.
All right, guys. I'm near the hatch key.
Please place. I'm right at it right now.
>> Oh, go.
>> Oh, come on. There's a [\h__\h] fence.
God damn it. to crawl all the way over
there.
>> These guys are taking forever.
>> This is people doesn't know how to play
the game. God damn.
>> I think they're fasting.
>> Okay, just come. I'll just
>> Oh, the shield.
>> Boom. Boom.
>> Okay, someone did a deadline
actually. Damn.
Oh,
>> is it over? It's not over.
>> It's It's over. It's over. It's over.
It's over,
>> actually. Loot. Loot. Loot. Loot. Loot.
Loot. Loot.
Go. Loot.
>> Uh, the bomb are still alive, by the
way. Be careful.
>> There's nothing here,
bro. Okay, I got it.
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. Okay, got
one major core.
>> That's it, Jack. Run away.
>> Someone's looting this.
>> Don't be greedy.
>> Always search for the core.
>> I'm at the hatch key place.
>> Ah, I'm not getting anything. Oh, I got
only one.
>> Should I leave before they try to, you
know,
>> raiders on screen?
>> Come quick.
>> I can open the hatch door.
>> I love Survivor.
Oh, there see run. See see. Oh, what a
jerk.
>> Oh my. I didn't even
>> never trust anyone. My god, this stupid
[\h__\h]
Are you dead? Dead.
Think you're dead. Dead. Okay, I'll go
first. Okay. Oh, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Don't wait for me.
I don't think you can make it.
>> He's still PvPing.
>> Jesus, what a jerk.
>> I don't I don't have anything. Please, n
the I forgot to keep it in my safe.
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
No,
bro.
>> You called it, too.
>> Shut up.
>> Wait, what's happening with my Oh, I'm
seeing your screen. Okay. Man, I'm out.
I'm out.
>> I called it, too.
Knocked out by Hamag. Okay, these are
Japanese players, bro.
Oh, that's an Indian player. Okay,
>> bro.
>> I swear Asian server are so boring.
They're so [\h__\h] boring. Uh,
at least I have the remote raider player
blueprint.
>> L I should have taken
>> the follow me.
>> Yeah,
>> you should have followed me. We killed
the bombader and we get more loot.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> Oh, well, that happened.
I don't lose anything too important.
You're just okay.
>> Crazy.
>> Want to go again? [laughter]
>> Probably switch server. You should go
into my server.
>> Yeah.
>> Make me the lead. Make me the leader.
Wait.
>> How do I do it that way?
Or can I invite you? You can out the
lobby and I invite you again.
>> Okay.
>> After this, I'll go go wrap up and
sleep. It's 1:30. Yep.
>> [\h__\h]
Last game. Okay. Last game. Last game.
>> Yep. Last game.
>> Throw this away.
The fact that the I mean that's how
everyone plays the game, right?
[laughter and gasps]
Rat and turn on each other. Get more
goop and leave.
>> What a shitty [\h__\h] server. Oh my god.
>> But crossplay is off. Is that the reason
why?
>> No, you shouldn't get less player like
people.
I mean, for my case, you're going to get
more toxic and PVP people if you uh play
with the console pe people.
Oh yeah,
>> that's for my case. How about yours?
>> I should have quickly put that in the
safe pocket.
Do you not
>> the matriarch or
man?
Hey, hatch key.
Uh, friend
invite. There we go.
>> Oh, I lost the blue one.
I lost my blue argument. Ah
>> [\h__\h] Blue Aman. Just blue.
Don't worry. Just a blue Aman.
>> Should I take survivor? I don't know.
>> Yeah, you could.
What's stopping you? You got to use it
anyway at one point.
Uh yeah,
I
crafted three of them.
>> Mhm.
>> The advanced electronic components is
hard to find, I guess. No, it's not
hard, but I have to
go in find it.
But yeah, that's how the game is, right?
>> Yep.
Okay, let me get my shield.
Let's bring a defe just in case.
That
>> I'm out of defense.
Damn.
Okay, let's go.
Bluegate harvester. Let's go.
>> Not the matriarch.
>> Yeah, it's done, I think.
>> Wait, what does harvester even do?
>> It's the queen.
>> Oh,
>> there's a big place where the queen is
guarding. There's a lot of loot. I have
never went inside there cuz people are
so quick.
Just just loot everything.
>> Should I take a shot? No, that's fine.
>> Bring a bruleta and a whole cracker.
>> I don't have that.
[snorts]
Wait. Do you have the anvil blueprint
already?
>> Uh, yeah, I do.
>> How did you get that? Wow.
>> I don't know.
Some random night raid.
Okay, almost done. Uh,
should I bring a wolfpack or something?
I'll take one.
I'm coming with the
>> rat though. Yeah.
>> Wait, what do you get from the queen?
What loot? the reactor. Kind of the same
with the uh matriarch but with the queen
reactor. But you got to have a queen
reactor.
>> I'm going to take the survivor. No,
wait. I'll take the
>> What? What? What argument did you take?
>> Revor. [laughter]
>> Okay, I'm going to take it. I hope and I
swear.
I don't want to die.
>> All I'm missing is just the um the basic
material.
>> Yeah, me too.
>> I need that those stuff so much. Okay,
let me just upgrade.
I need steel spring. See, I need the
spring. My god.
>> Ready up.
>> Okay. Uh you bought the hash key, right?
Yep.
>> Okay.
>> All right.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Shove it in your eyeball.
>> Okay.
>> A queen here.
>> Anyone fighting it?
>> [\h__\h] They're fighting each other. No,
that's not
the
>> supply.
>> Aren't we finding a queen?
>> Oh my god, I'm I'm lagging at 1 FPS.
>> No.
Oh, they are. Let's go. Let's go.
Have you ever fight a queen?
>> Nope. First time.
>> What?
So they have more um more weapon than
just the uh
Are you [\h__\h] Oh my
with three bullets. Oh my god.
Jesus Christ. The hell.
Oh my god.
Don't shoot.
>> Is there people?
>> Yeah.
>> Where?
>> It saw me. It saw me.
If we had a deadline, we could have
jumped on top of it and literally
What is that? here.
>> That's uh energy shield or something.
>> Yeah, let's go here.
>> My game laggy.
Oh my god. Wait.
>> Hello. Hello.
>> My game UI is bugged. Oh my god. What is
this?
>> Oh my god. Try to open my stream. This
is so funny. This is so funny.
>> Someone
>> open my stream and check.
>> Hold on. Someone's dead.
>> Why is this
>> Why is it close?
>> Oh, when the fire is happening.
>> Hello. Are we cool?
>> Oh, come on. Don't close on me.
Oh, is it going to blow up?
>> It's my first time in here. Oh, what the
[\h__\h]
>> Wait, is there They're like PvP.
>> No, no, no. It's the reactor.
>> I thought it's going to open fire or
something.
Oh. Oh, yeah.
>> Oh my.
They did that. [\h__\h] hell.
>> My game froze. My game froze. Oh my god.
My game froze.
>> Oh, get a safe spot. Get to a safe spot.
>> Did I die? Did I die?
>> No. No, you're not. You're not.
>> I forgot to get shields.
I'm so dumb.
>> Careful. No.
>> Ah,
my game is dying.
>> Come here. Come here. Come here.
>> I wanted to loot upstairs and get some
blueprint or something if there is any.
>> You might get shocked.
Where are you? Oh, you're there.
Are they PvP?
>> Wait, don't say PVP like that.
>> Oh no, it's a matriarch and the queen.
[\h__\h] What are they doing?
>> Wait, did you die,
>> bro? Come on.
Oh, they killed me. Come, come, come.
Seriously.
Can you revive me?
No.
>> But did they actually kill you?
>> Yeah, they're just greedy with the loot.
>> Damn.
>> Yeah, we got it.
>> I looted everything. Oh my god, how fast
are they?
I notic
energy ammo.
>> Oh my god,
>> my PC is dying over here. Oh my god.
Okay,
>> get down. Get down. Wait, you you're
still in the fire. [\h__\h]
I'm coming out.
>> Yeah, we should get out. Oh my god.
>> Are you going to actually revive me
here? Okay.
>> Let's just get the [\h__\h] out.
>> The harvester is scary.
>> I know there's a lot of people looting
it. That's why they could get super
greedy.
Wait, actually, did someone die or
>> Let's get a safe spot and then try shoot
it.
>> It's actually guarding the
harvester with its life.
>> That's why the the queen is way harder
than the freaking
careful
>> on me.
Thank you.
What happened?
>> Oh my
got shot. Get in. Get in. Don't have
shield.
>> Get inside.
Oh [\h__\h]
Got one of the legs.
Oh [\h__\h] I got stump on.
>> Don't die.
>> Ow.
>> Get inside.
>> Trying to
Okay, get in.
I got the reactor. [laughter]
I got the reactor.
Okay, I'm out of shield. I need a still
have a light one thankfully.
>> Oh my god. Here.
>> Have this.
have this.
>> I'm stuck at what? What? How?
>> There's a leg.
>> Nice.
Thank you.
Did that guy just [\h__\h] loot this? Oh,
you [\h__\h] ass little [\h__\h] rat.
Ah, snitch.
Uh, could you kill the
Ah, did it call the backup?
>> No. No, it did not.
>> I think it did. No. Okay, it didn't.
>> Yeah. Let me try to shoot it from here.
>> Oh my god.
Woo. Careful.
>> I'm dead. I'm dead.
It spits fire.
Okay,
>> let me kill that freaking stupid WS.
My broke. Oh my god, my shield broken.
>> No.
>> And you still not dead. Oh my. This was
I'm going to craft some shield recharger
or something somehow.
We need to get the second lag.
>> Okay, take your time. Take your time. Is
it like lagging on stream or lag the
game?
>> My game is lagging so much. It's at 10
FPS.
Oh, it's spit dragon fire.
Oh boy.
Wait, did you get a reactor car?
>> Yeah, I have one.
>> Okay, nice.
Oh, it's about to explode.
It's going to die soon.
It's dead. It's dead. It's dead. It's
set. Go, go, go, go, go. I'm coming.
>> Really?
>> Oh, someone got it first. [\h__\h] God damn
it.
Get ready,
>> dude. You're such a [\h__\h] rat.
>> How miserable you are, dude.
>> Dragon revive me.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Good one. He's on the roof. He's on the
roof. Yuck. You have to revive me. I'm
right in front of you.
It's so [\h__\h] pitive.
My god, that guy.
>> That guy is so [\h__\h] miserable. I
swear to God. The guy with the golden
mast thing.
>> Lexi. Lexi.
making one. I'm I'm leaving.
>> Where's that guy?
Where the [\h__\h] is he? I'm going to spit
on him.
>> Wait, did he die?
>> Yeah. Is it?
>> No, not this guy. This guy's already
looted.
Uh, let me see. There's some stuff. No.
>> Oh, I have the hatch key. I can can use
the hatch.
>> Where's that guy?
Oh, let's leave. Let's leave.
>> Not this guy. This guy's right.
>> Oh, this guy.
>> No, no, no. Not him. Not him.
>> Don't do that.
Oh my god. They'll kill you.
>> Why did they kill you?
>> Come, come, come. Let's leave. Let's
leave. Let's leave. Uh, rocket here.
Rocket here.
>> Oh, here. Let me
>> help this folks.
Hold on. Let me help them.
Woohoo.
Are these the queen spots? Okay, it is.
>> Hey, Alexa, leave together.
>> One sec. I'm going to loot this rocket
here.
I got the rocketeer thingy. Nice.
>> We can go to the uh
>> Where's the hatch key?
>> Yeah.
>> Just to be safe.
See, at least in this [\h__\h] server,
people talking to each other.
Yeah.
Oh, PVP PVP PVP.
A rat. A rat.
>> Okay. Come in. Coming. Coming. Coming.
>> Bacon.
Bacon. [\h__\h]
>> guys, let's leave.
>> Oh my god,
bro. Don't tell me. I'm like,
we got to handle the rat. No rat
allowed.
>> I got him. I got him. I got him.
>> You want to loot? Want to loot them?
>> Did you kill everyone?
Go to one. Explain yourself. Explain
yourself then. Come on.
>> How do they threaten? I don't hear gun.
I I hear no gunshots.
>> They didn't know.
>> I only heard one set of gunshots.
>> Execute them. They're horrible people.
You don't get to sit there and rat when
everyone was working together. [\h__\h] you.
[laughter]
There's a blue letter in his body.
>> He [\h__\h] Wait, no. So, the other two
just like
>> Yeah, they're just dead.
>> There's only one gun sound right from
one direction.
>> Yeah, it was literally just one set of
gunshots.
>> If they fighting each other, we would
know.
>> They They had full shield. So, like
there was no way that these two could
have like gotten a shot off.
>> They're probably
>> This guy had a free load out, too.
>> Hold on.
>> I got exit.
>> Hell yeah.
Rat terminated.
>> Uh, that
>> you see my point? Yeah.
[laughter]
Wait, which server did you choose
though?
>> Yeah, just my server that I'm playing
NA.
>> Like what's the reason?
>> I don't know.
>> Na.
In the end, there were only four.
[laughter]
>> I'm so happy I have two quining reactor,
two rocketeer
Let's get the [\h__\h] home, boys.
>> GG's everyone.
>> I repeat,
>> nice.
>> Oh, feel good killing that rat.
[laughter]
>> Feel so good killing that rat. Okay, let
me see how much damage I deal to him.
>> Nice.
>> Knocked out. Oh, I knocked him down.
Okay. Okay. Bullet time. [laughter]
>> I never shot anyone in this game ever so
far.
>> Uh, you got to be tough. You have to
show them your ground.
If not, you're just going to get killed.
>> That's true.
You got a torrent from one another guy.
>> I got like uh borleta two bulletas from
the dead bodies. Yeah.
>> Nice.
>> Oh my god.
>> What the hell was that [clears throat]
guy who killed me?
>> Scied.
>> So, how many rats were there? Three.
Four.
>> Three. Three rats.
>> Where the rest of the people? There were
like so many people though.
>> Yeah, I know. See, the rat has no shame.
[laughter]
>> Wait, did you loot the dead bodies of
other people or did they all revive each
other?
>> Uh, what? What do you mean?
>> Uh, like the rad killed three people,
right? They were like three uh three or
four.
>> Two. Two. Two people.
>> Two. Okay.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I already looted them. They
on a free load out.
>> Wait, so I think they're the rat. No.
Which one is the rat? [laughter]
>> Oh, well,
I just need one more motor.
I have how many
I have? Oh, just one and then one
rocketeer driver. Not bad.
I'm saving the loot thing survival
blueprint. Some for some reason I like
if I have this in early game. No, then
it's OP, right?
>> Like if from a fresh Yeah.
But can't they like uh family thingy do
the family thingy and like use a
different Steam account? Is that
possible for paid games?
>> No. Yeah, you can use Steam uh family.
Yeah, for this game.
>> Oh yeah. Oh.
I might actually. I don't know.
But you have to trade. Oh, wait. How
will I play two accounts though?
Yeah, you can only one play one account.
That's the thing.
>> All right. You going to wrap up?
>> Yeah, I'll wrap up. Mhm.
>> Okay.
>> I'm happy I got two reactors.
>> That's
okay. You get wrapped up. See you, J.
See you. See you.
>> See you.
>> Yes.
Let me just sell this.
Okay.
I leave a cup. Take care.
Hi.
Yeah, it's 2 a.m. Uh, we've been playing
for a while now, right?
>> We have been playing for a while. Thank
you, Bacon, for carrying me. And we
finally got the reactor turquoise. Nice.
I'm happy.
Yay.
I'm not sure if I'm lagging right now,
but uh my stream was the game was
lagging so much today. Crazy.
Oh, super lagging.
It's even now lagging, too.
[sighs and gasps]
Uh [groaning]
oh, there was someone on Oh, there was
someone on beam. Thank you for watching.
Isel,
bro, I really need to keep the beam beam
beam stream chat somewhere.
Yeah,
honestly.
Uh
well
uh one second.
Where is it? Oh my god. Where is it?
Anyway, hi. Uh, I will wrap it up over
here.
It was really nice
to
game tonight.
Tomorrow, oh, it's already 15th. Okay,
so to today is the last day I will be. I
mean, tomorrow I'll be there. I don't
know if I'll stream actually. I'll be
traveling tomorrow night. Probably
uh tomorrow night or Saturday I will be
traveling.
Yeah, 16th.
Uh so yeah, exams and stuff I'll have to
revise and stuff.
I'm kind of planning to
do a Anki revision
stream tomorrow. I'm not sure.
I could
I could do it, but I don't know.
Oh, yeah. I feel Oh, is this weekend?
Oh, I feel so stressed these days cuz I
have to no matter what pass this exam.
There's that, too.
But yeah,
I'll give my best shot. Everyone,
I'll give my best shot. Yeah.
Wait, what happened? Why can't I
redirect? Oh,
what?
Wait, why can't I?
Wait, the V channel is not streaming or
something. What?
Oh my god. Wait, did the V channel die?
I died. Oh god, no.
Wait, is Twitch working?
Uh
the amount of issues I'm having to face
I I I'm feeling like
is it the G um PC issue or Okay, it just
YouTube died. Okay, I mean it's been 3
weeks now when I started that stream.
So I think it's almost time for it to
reset or something weird but okay.
Hey. Oh, we actually streamed for 4
hours. Wow.
Oh, nice.
What over 30 minutes? Nice. I think this
is the longest stream I actually did in
a week.
I actually stream for this long.
Nice.
Uh
me a minute. Let me just fix up these
stuff and like
uh
do stuff.
Uh
uh
one and
clip order make last stick a clip.
Okay. Uh I have to log to
what channel and then do this.
Huh? How did it die though?
Video is processing.
Uh, even join a stream chat. Try it out.
I'll have to make a new one, huh?
13.
Okay.
the amount of things.
Okay,
I have to do
multi melt and
restart the feed.
Oh, kick also died. Oh.
Oh,
kickstream also died.
Man, that sucks.
Pink. Yeah, we are wrapping up. Yep.
Yep. Yep.
I'm wrapping up.
Uh
my
my 24x7 channel just died. So, I was
restarting the um restarting the feed so
I can read my 24x7 channel.
Uh okay. Okay. Kick is live.
Wait, wait. Is it live or is it dead?
Okay, it's live.
Yeah. What channel is active? Okay,
good. Uh, Twitch is also good. Okay,
I'll start the Wait, I never tried
reading uh hosting on
on kick. How do I do that?
Let me find this top next.
Redirect on YouTube.
Why is there I can't find my own
channel. What the heck? What?
Dark X,
bro.
What?
What? Okay, it is not. Why?
Uh
nope.
Okay. Uh oh my god, so many mosquitoes
today.
Search for videos. I praise this.
Oh my god. Why is it not? Okay, let me
restart this. Refresh the page. So, let
me just
do it.
Who is this guy?
Stop doing rerun.
Wait, what?
How come I did not read the chat?
Wait.
Hello.
You see this?
Where? When did this person when did
penguin soldier message?
What the heck?
Am I not Why is my kick chat not showing
up? What the heck?
Did I not reconnected? Oh my god,
I hate this so much. Streamer bot. What
happened? Oh my god, it's
ah
connect.
It was not connected.
stop doing rerun sims. Uh it I'm doing
the 24x7 channel for a reason.
Uh
yeah,
I already explained it in a video
though.
I mean,
it's for those who want to just uh watch
older streams.
Uh that's why it's made on a separate
channel.
No one is entitled or required or forced
to watch that.
If you want to use it as background
background uh noise and just keep the
stream in the background, you you can
you can
but it's basically not required to like
uh watch those streams.
I'm only doing it because uh this year
by April onwards I won't be able to
stream by my PC at home. I'm going to
use it as a server when I'm in Japan. So
I'll use my PC at home in India to like
do the 2477 channel so that uh those who
want to watch old content they can watch
it right that's why I separated
and that's why I made a new kick channel
for it.
Yeah.
How do I host on
uh
how do I host, bro?
Oh, you sent that message at 9:52. Oh,
that's so bad.
But wait, I'm so confused about
something. Is people not able to
distinguish between a actual live stream
and a act
channel live stream?
Uh,
is it because
Oh my god. Do I have to make it that
obvious now?
I feel like I should make it more
obvious.
I need for
contact.
Uh,
oh my god, I sent that message, bro.
How much? Oh my god.
Anyway, I'll just wrap up, man. I don't
want to.
Too many issues. Just doing a simple
stream. Too many issues. Haha.
Uh, okay. What channel is live?
I'm going to end it here. Thank you all
for coming by. I really went a lot. All
right. I'll work on some stuff for the
war channel after my exams are over.
Okay. I want to automate this thingy
somehow.
It's so annoying to like always spit in
the comment all the time or um
tell people like,
"Yeah, this is a VOD, not actual
stream."
Uh, a lot of streamers are doing it. I'm
just doing it, too.
Uh,
yeah.
Anyway, I'll send you guys to my V
channel. Anyone take care.
Hi.
We are wrapping it up.
So, once again, thank you all for coming
by tonight.
See you in the next stream.
two fight
now. What happened? Oh my god.
So many crashes. I'm going to
Anya, I'll wrap it up. Oh my god.
Hi. One day I'll be able to stream
peacefully one day, guys. Hi. Anyway,
good night. Have a good one, everyone.
Bye-bye. Good night. Good night. Good
night.